const THE = [
  {
    id: 1,
    front: "ὁ",
    back: ["Case: Nominative", "Gender: M", "Person: (s.)"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: "τόν",
    back: ["Case: Accusative", "Gender: M", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 3,
    front: "τοῠ",
    back: ["Case: Genitive", "Gender: M or N", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 4,
    front: "τῷ",
    back: ["Case: Dative", "Gender: M or N", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 5, 
    front: "ή",
    back: ["Case: Nominative", "Gender: F", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 6,
    front: "τήν",
    back: ["Case: Accusative", "Gender: F", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 7,
    front: "τῆς",
    back: ["Case: Genitive", "Gender: F", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 8,
    front: "τῇ",
    back: ["Case: Dative", "Gender: F", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 9,
    front: "τό",
    back: ["Case: Nominative or Accusative", "Gender: N", "Person: (s.)"]
  }, {
    id: 10,
    front: "οί",
    back: ["Case: Nominative", "Gender: M", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 11,
    front: "τούς",
    back: ["Case: Accusative", "Gender: M", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 12,
    front: "τῶν",
    back: ["Case: Genative", "Gender: M or F or N", "Person: (pl.)"]
  } , {
    id: 13,
    front: "τοῖς",
    back: ["Case: Dative", "Gender: M or N", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 14,
    front: "αί",
    back: ["Case: Nominatve", "Gender: F", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 15,
    front: "τᾱς",
    back: ["Case: Accusative", "Gender: F", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 16,
    front: "ταῖς",
    back: ["Case: Dative", "Gender: F", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }, {
    id: 17,
    front: "τά",
    back: ["Case: Nominative or Accusative", "Gender: N", "Person: (pl.)"]
  }
];

export default THE;